Raul Mateo Beneyto

Software Engineer

I am a self-driven person who enjoys learning and creating all kinds of projects. Not only I relish working as a team as it requires communication and dedication, but also I have an open mind to new ideas and appreciate learning from others with more knowledge and experience. In addition, I am a positive person who enjoys maintaining the enthusiasm in a work environment.



✓ raulmateob@gmail.com

Barcelona, Spain

in Raul Mateo Beneyto

+34 691014930

raulmabe.dev

Rahuvich

EDUCATION

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering majored in Software Engineering

Sep. 2015 - Dec. 2020

Personal Projects at raulmabe.dev

Love trying new technologies, tools, patterns and techniques. I encourage you to check some of my projects in my website, where I show some mock-ups along with an explanation about each one.

always

EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer at iThinkUPC

As part of a multi-disciplinary web development team, I was responsible for the development and maintenance of a multi-user web application.

- MVC Architecture
- Java, SpringBoot, Lombok, Hibernate
- Scrum and Kanban Board with Jira

Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Front-end Developer at Jumpets

As a member of a *start-up*, I developed a website and a multiplatform application.

- MVC Architecture
- Flutter, BLoC and Redux patterns
- PHP, Laravel and Blade

Jun. 2019 - Sep. 2020

PROGRAMMING

★ Flutter

★ Dart

★ JavaScript ★ ReactJS

NodeJS

GatsbyJS

SASS

CSS

SpringBoot

• C++

★ Java

★ GraphQL

 TypeScript Linux CLI

• (

KNOWLEDGE

- ★ UI/UX Design
- ★ Software Architecture
- Agile methodologies
- Good coding practices
- Testing and TDD
- Search Engine Optimization
- Internationalization
- Desing Patterns

TOOLS

- Git / Github
- Slack
- Kanban boards
- Lighthouse
- Chrome DevTools
 iOS/Android Simulators
- Figma
- IDEs

COMMUNITY

I try to collaborate in open source and build community among IT students by attending hackathons.

LANGUAGES

English B2 • **Spanish** native • **Catalan** native